Guide to the Religious Organizations and Activities, Yale University, Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Religious organizations and activities, Yale University, photographs
1893-1962
RU 764
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3.5
Photographs of Yale students engaged in religious events or activities at St. Thomas More, Dwight Hall, and Bethany Sunday School.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 39-A (YRG 39-A), Records documenting official religious activities at Yale.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by subject.
Scope and Contents
Photographs of Yale students engaged in religious events or activities at St. Thomas More, Dwight Hall, and Bethany Sunday School.
College students -- Religious life; Photographs; Yale University -- Religion; Yale University -- Students
- Photographs, Series I
  - Photographs (regular size), circa 1942-1962 (Box 1)
  - Oversize
    - Byers Hall, YMCA Academic Senior Council (SSS), 1914 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Dwight Hall YMCA
      - Executive Committee, 1893-1911 (Box 2, Folder 2-4)
      - Bethany Sunday School, circa 1904, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Executive Committee, 1905-1914 (Box 2, Folder 6-8)
      - Cabinet, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Executive Committee Hall, 1915-1917 (Box 3, Folder 10-11)
      - Cabinet, 1917-1918,1931-1933 (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
      - Cabinet, 1941, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Hillel (Cabinets), 1947-1961 (Box 3, Folder 15-17)